(Sheldon:)Mrs. Wunch in fourth grade.
(Sheldon:)And my slogan was
“a line that's straight
is a line that's great”"
(Man:)Is this guy for real?
(Leonard:)Boy, I wish
I could say no.
(Beverly:)That was very nice
of Sheldon to apologize.
(Amy:)Well, he's come a long way.
(Amy:)Or a short way very slowly,
(Amy:)so it feels like a long way.
(Beverly:)Your relationship
with him is fascinating.
(Beverly:)I'm preparing to write a book
on high-achieving couples,
(Beverly:)and I would love to
interview the both of you.
(Amy:)Oh, sure.
I'll-I'll talk
to Sheldon about it.
(Amy:)You know, Bernadette's husband
is a former astronaut.
(Beverly:)Really?
(Beverly:)Do you think
he would be interested
(Beverly:)in being interviewed
as well?
(Bernadette:)Do I think he'd be interested?
(Bernadette:)Sometimes I hear him
pretending to be interviewed
(Bernadette:)when he's alone
in the bathroom.
Wonderful!
(Amy:)I'll give you
my contact information.
(Bernadette:)Um, you should probably
talk to Penny, too.
(Beverly:)About what?